A Guide to the Ancel E. Nunn Papers, 1943-2008
Nunn, Ancel E., Papers
1943-2008
Nunn, Ancel E.
2008-252
36 feet, 5 inches
Dolph Briscoe Center for American History, The University of Texas at Austin
Correspondence, artworks, notes, financial documents, legal documents, photographs, audiovisual material, and printed material document the artwork, business operations, and personal life of Ancel Edward Nunn, an acclaimed Texas artist known for his super-realism style and acrylic in egg tempera technique.
Biographical Note
Ancel Edward Nunn (1928-1999) was an acclaimed artist known for his super-realism style and acrylic in egg tempera technique. Born on April 27, 1928, in Seymour, Texas, Nunn grew up in several West Texas communities. His early art education included studying at the Dallas Art Institute at age 15 and attending summer workshops under artists such as Dong Kingman and Alexandre Hogue. Nunn served in the United States Army Reserve with intermittent periods of active duty from 1947 until his honorable discharge with the rank of Major in 1969. He did little painting in the military, until 1963 when he met his future wife Reneta, who supported his decision to become a professional artist. Between 1964 and 1967, Nunn searched for a personal style and philosophy of painting, during which time he destroyed many of the paintings he produced. In 1969 Nunn moved to Palestine, Texas, where he set up a studio called The Foundry and continued painting. Nunn moved again in 1980 to his new Morningtown Studio east of Palestine, where he began to create lithographs in addition to paintings. Exhibitions of Nunn’s works have been held at the Tyler Museum of Art, Lyndon B. Johnson Library, Museum of East Texas, and the University of Texas at Tyler. His work was published in Ancel E. Nunn: A Timeless World, And Where Goes the Parade, and many magazines and other publications. Nunn also illustrated several works for A.C. Greene and Leon Hale and his works inspired the poetry of Samuel Woolvin in Remnants of Change. Ancel Nunn died on December 24, 1999.
Scope and Contents
Correspondence, artworks, notes, financial documents, legal documents, photographs, audiovisual material, and printed material document Ancel Nunn’s artwork, business operations, and personal life. The bulk of the papers are Ancel Nunn’s, but a small subgroup of Reneta Nunn’s papers (4 inches) is included.
The Personal series (1945-2002, 1 linear foot) details Nunn’s personal history, philosophy, and thoughts about art and life, and includes materials associated with his memorial. Executed artworks files (1969-2008, undated, 7 linear feet) include ownership records of created artworks, exhibition records, correspondence, and photographs. Patron files (1968-2008, 4 linear feet) include business records of patron holdings, correspondence, and printed material.
Correspondence (1957-2008) is divided into two subseries, General (1967-2008, 2 linear feet), arranged chronologically, and Selected (1957, 1972-2008, 1 linear foot), arranged alphabetically. Selected work files (1968-2008, 4 linear feet) document Nunn’s working relationships and collaborations, and contain correspondence, original artwork, manuscripts, photographs, audiovisual material, and printed material. Notable work files include Samuel Woolvin, A.C. Greene, Billy Porterfield, and Yevgeny Yevtushenko.
Exhibition files (1971-2008, 1.5 linear feet) document Nunn’s artwork exhibitions. Log books (1975-2000, 2 linear feet) are Nunn’s daily log of activities. Art series includes original artwork created and acquired by Ancel Nunn. Other series include Awards (1977-1978, 3 inches), Financial (1968-2002, .5 linear feet), Guest books (1971-2001, .4 linear feet), Newspaper clippings (1947-2007, 4 inches), Magazines (1971-2005, 4 inches), Miscellaneous records (1995-2000, undated, 3 inches), and Photographs (1968-2001, 1 linear foot).
Archivist's Note
The Executed artworks series is arranged by Nunn’s own system, where the first two numbers indicate the year the artwork was created and last two digits indicate the artwork number that year. This series also contained several empty folders, which were not retained. The folder titles are 6501 Shacks And Mailboxes, 6609 Bench #2, 6610 Small Landscape, 6611 Childhood Memory, 6928 House With Stone Wall, 6930 View From The Upper Window, 7024 Old Homeplace, 7025 Wagon Barn, 7142 Fence Line, 7244 Study of House, 7245 Study of Willet, 7246 Shirey Barn – Watercolor Study, and 7328 Light Study of Baskets Bucket.
Ancel Nunn’s original file system was maintained as much as possible. One exception is that his Selected files were divided into Selected correspondence and Selected work files. Selected correspondence files are primarily personal or non-work-related correspondence. Selected work files document Nunn’s working relationships and collaborations.
Access Restrictions
This collection is open for research use.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Nunn, Ancel E.; Woolvin, Samuel C. (Samuel Carmon); Greene, A. C., 1923-; Porterfield, Bill; Yevtushenko, Yevgeny Aleksandrovich, 1933-
Subjects
Art--Texas; Artists--Texas; Art, American--Texas--20th century; Art, American--Texas--Exhibitions
Detailed Description of the Papers
- Stored remotely at Library Storage Facility (LSF):
  - Ancel Nunn papers 1943-2008
    - Personal 1945-2002 (Box 2008-252/1)
      - Biography undated (Box 2008-252/1)
      - Early personal history 1945-1967, 1997 (Box 2008-252/1)
      - Family history 1964, 1985-1999 (Box 2008-252/1)
      - Philosophy/thoughts undated (Box 2008-252/1)
      - Philosophy study materials undated (Box 2008-252/1)
      - Memorial 1999-2000 (Box 2008-252/1)
      - Assorted 1965-2002 (Box 2008-252/1)
    - Executed artworks files 1969-2008, undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 4301 – 4302 undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 5001 Horses undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 5002 Red Snapper Fisherman undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6201 Mexican Boy undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 64 – 67A Early Ancel Nunn Works 64-67, Tavernetti collection, undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6401 Two Brothers undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6402 House On Stilts undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6403 The Moaners undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6404 Death of a Child undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6405 Boy With Chicken undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6406 Lonely Goose undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6407 Portrait of Jimmy Young Sons undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 650A Boy on Sidewalk With Poster Puzzle undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6502 Boy With Kite undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6503 Madonna With Child undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6504 Release of Emotions undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6505 Portrait of Reneta undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6601 The Tire undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6602 Fortune Teller undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6603 Treasure Shell undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6604 Road Up undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6605 The Beggars undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6606 The Parade undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6607 The Hero undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6608 Number Seven undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6612 Barn undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6613 Dusty Road undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6614 Mother w. Child undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 67A Boy With Ring Puzzle 1994, undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 67B “Feed Store” “Store Fronts” 1995, undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 67C Spring 2001, undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 67D Sunday House / Texas Hill Country undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 67E Silo With Barn undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 67F Clothpins undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6701 Waiting Game undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6702 Cactus With Birds undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6703 Apartment House undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6704 The Farmer undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6705 Tamale Stand undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6706 Caliente undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6707 Current News undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6708 The Baker undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6709 The Musician undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6710 Morning Coffee #1 undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6711 Old School undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6712 Bandstand undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6713 Blacksmith Shop undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6714 Sunday Afternoon undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6715 Boy With Puzzle undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6716 Feed Store undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6717 Six Thirty undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6718 Passed By undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6719 Old Axe undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6720 Thirsty undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6721 Hope 1976, undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6722 Sagging Barn undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6723 Gazebo undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6724 Tent Show undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6725 Good Morning undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6726 Boy With Kite #2 2003, undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6727 Boy On Sidewalk undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6728 Forgotten Memories undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6729 Mexican Man With Hen undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6730 Far Away 1981, undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6731 Keys undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6732 German Farm House undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6733 Road To Nowhere undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6734 The Window undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6735 The Pitcher Pump 1975-1976, undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6736 Bird On Clothesline undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6737 Cider Waxwing undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6738 Waiting Game, 2 Mexican Ladies undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6739 Squeak 1978, undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6740 Nickel Coke and Penny Matches undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6741 Baa, Baa Black Sheep 2004, undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6742 House at the end of the Street undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6743 Magic Time Machines undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 68A Anderson, Texas Courthouse undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6801 Nails A Go Go undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6802 German Farm House, #2 undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6803 East Texas Log undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6804 Plow At Luckenbach undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6805 The Door of the Widow Lopez undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6806 Rear View Horse undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6807 Ancel Paul 1992, undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - Don’t Step on My Railroad 1991, undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6809 The Hinge undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6810 Objects undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6811 Windmill Road undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6812 San Marcos Depot undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6813 Signs of the Time undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6814 Freight Depot undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6815 Hopscotch undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6816 Funeral of A.J. Hamilton 1969, undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6817 Old Bank undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6818 Railroad Bridge undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6819 Woman At Luckenbach undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6820 Approaching Storm 1971, undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6821 Leapfrog undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6822 Red Sneakers undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6823 Rolling undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6824 Bright Early Barn undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6825 Fischers Store undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6826 Benno Engel, Luckenbach Postmaster 1995-2003, undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6827 Cherry House undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6828 House Near El Campo undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6829 Hill Country House undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6830 Boys On Scooter undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6831 Staircase Windows undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6832 Windows undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6833 House In Anderson undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6834 South Texas Monument undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6835 Remember Me undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6836 Circus Poster undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6837 Shanghai Pierce Hotel undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6838 The Funeral undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6839 Deserted Farm In Fredericksburg County undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6840 Rain Barrel undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6841 The Sexton undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6842 Untitled (Barn) 67-68? undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6843 House By the Edge of Time undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6901 Smiling Barn undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6902 Step on a Crack undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6903 Birds on Tree Limb undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6904 The Lane undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6905 Itan Flat undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6906 Whitewash Wall undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6907 Ice Wagon undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6908 Benno Engel 1995-2000, undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6909 Front Fence Post 1982, undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6910 House Beside the Road undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6911 Sunday Morning undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6912 Mail Boxes undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6913 Window With Quilt undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6914 Racing The Storm undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6915 Yesterday, Today, and Tomorrow undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6916 Circus Barn undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6917 Boy On A Horse undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6918 Neches, Texas undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6919 Soaring undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6920 Monday Morning undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6921 Soft Drink undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6922 The Eggman undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6923 Barn With Poster undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6924 The Meeting Place undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6925 Bright Early #1 undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6926 Catarina, South Texas undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6927 House With Three Horses undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6929 Iron Butterflies undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 6931 ??? 1976 (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 6932 ??? undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 6933 Boy scribbling on sidewalk undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 6934 House at the Edge of Time 1995, undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7001 Brown Shoes 2003, undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7002 Train Station undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7003 Broken Window undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7004 The Road to Town undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7005 Stone Barn undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7006 Hill Country House, 2 undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7007 Two Friends undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7008 East Texas Store undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7009 Frankston Depot undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7010 Water Point undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7011 Candy Break undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7012 Domino Parlor 1977, undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7013 Patelax Wagon undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7014 Mount Vernon Church undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7015 Limestone undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7016 Greatest Show on Earth undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7017 Revival 1977, undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7018 Road Home undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7019 The Ant Watcher undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7020 Cloudy undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7021 The Treasure undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7022 Luckenbach Store undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7023 Road To House undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7026 Blacksmith Shop in Blanco, TX undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7027 Swing at Coyote School undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7028 Barnum Bailey Poster undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7029 Back Door in Albany undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7101 The Cook Store undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7102 Old Store 1975-1978, undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7103 Grain Barrel undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7104 Clothesline undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7105 Bright Early 1977, undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7106 Objects on a Hill undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7107 Under the House undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7108 The Intruder undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7109 Edge of the Woods undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7110 The Table 1976, undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7111 Money, Marbles, Chalk undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7112 Bright Early undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7113 Wasp Nest undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7114 Railroad Crossing undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7115 Barn Door at Panna Maria undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7116 The Bucket undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7117 The Fireplace undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7118 Onions undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7119 Old Rip undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7120 The Tenant House undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7121 South Porch undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7122 View From Southside undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7123 Abandoned Cafe undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7124 The Lone Sentry undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7125 Ruins At Panna Maria undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7126 Steamboat, Texas undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7127 Veterans Day undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7128 Door On the Hay Barn undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7129 Morning Coffee undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7130 The Farmer undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7131 A Summer’s Day undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7132 Wedding Day undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7133 Noonday [1971?]-1974 (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7134 Hay Barn undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7135 Turn in the Road undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7136 Saturday Morning undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7137 Homeplace 1983, undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7138 Down the Road undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7139 Southside Window [1971?-1978?] (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7140 Wagon undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7141 Planter undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7143 Bottles in Commissary undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7144 Bobby’s Friend undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7145 Ear of Corn undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7146 The Cistern undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7147 The Day the Wind Blew undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7148 Castroville German House undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7149 Hilltop undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7150 The Gaines Farm Homestead undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7151 “Circus Poster, 1934” [1971?], 1982 (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7201 The Gleaners undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7202 North Zulch Depot undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7203 Mission Orange undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7204 Study of an Old Store undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7205 Number One undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7206 Front View Number One undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7207 Number Five undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7208 Moscow, Camden, San Augustine undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7209 Sisterdale School undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7210 Where Go the Boats undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7211 Unbound undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7212 Farmers Bank [1972?]-1974 (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7213 The Wasp Nest undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7214 Saturday Morning undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7215 Back Door undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7216 Hot Box at Wells Switch undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7217 The Log undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7218 A Cool Summer Day undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7219 Waiting for the 12:15 undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7220 Sweet Season undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7221 Butterfly Chair undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7222 Bright Early Coffee Tea #5 undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7223 Four Seasons undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7224 Neches Depot undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7225 A Quiet Place undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7226 Change of Season undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7227 Buttermilk Glass undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7228 The Lodge Hall undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7229 Under the Porch undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7230 Preacher’s Window undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7231 Washing Up undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7232 Day’s Work undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7233 The Investigator undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7234 Christmas Past undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7235 Storehouse Window undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7236 Storehouse Door undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7237 Providence Church undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7238 701 Reagan Street 1972-1978 (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7239 839 Tennessee Avenue undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7240 The Davis House undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7241 The Pecan Tree undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7241 The Spot undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7243 Log Cabin undated (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7301 Rainwater [1973?]-1976, 1991 (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7302 A Bowl of Springtime 1973-[circa 1978], 1995 (Box 2008-252/3)
      - 7303 Calling the Cows undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7304 The Piper 1977, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7305 Saturday Afternoon undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7306 Where Goes the Parade undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7307 Monument Hill 1978, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7308 Bright Early Morning 1977, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7309 Through a Glass Darkly undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7310 Pandora undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7311 The Path undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7312 Suppertime 1977, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7313 The Distant Whistle 1978, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7314 Watching the Cars Go By undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7315 The Visitor undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7316 It Must Be Raining in Roscoe undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7317 Harbinger 1977, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7318 The Race undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7319 Summer Wind undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7320 The Road and Beyond undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7321 Number Five – 197321 undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7322 Hickornuts undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7323 Study of a Domino Game undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7324 Carter Bro #5 undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7325 Portrait of Dr. Harry A. Haverlah undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7326 Cottage on Church Street 1973, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7327 Gingerbread Cottage undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7329 Spivey’s Store 1973 (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7330 Study of 3 Baskets undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7331 Grade Crossing undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7332 The Memory Box undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7333 Church at Shiloh undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7334 The Gift undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7335 Sunday at Shiloh 1973 (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7336 Old Friend 1973 (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7337 The Gate undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7338 The Coon Hunt 1985, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7339 Bucket Basket undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7339 Bucket Basket undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7401 Afternoon Sun undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7402 Days of the Giants 1978, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7403 Road to the Sea undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7404 Key to the City 1977, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7405 Prodigal Son undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7406 Flint, Texas undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7407 The Brass Ring undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7408 Fourth of July 1981, 1999-2000, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7409 To See Ourselves undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7410 Out to Pasture 1976 (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7411 The Blue Apron undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7412 The Chalk House undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7413 Youth undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7414 The Maze undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7415 Another Day undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7416 Metamorphosis 1977, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7417 The Blue Barn undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7418 The Tide Line undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7419 Voices in the Wind 1977, 1990, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7420 The Wanderer 1977, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7421 A Secret Place undated (Box 2008-252/4)